<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--content/coc/desert.xml-->
<extend-zone name="desert" xmlns="xxc-story">
    <lib name="strings">
        <lib name="chest">
            <text name="a">
                While wandering the trackless sands of the desert, you break the silent monotony with a loud 'thunk'.
                You look down and realize you're standing on the lid of an old chest, somehow intact and buried in the sand.
                Overcome with curiosity, you dig it out, only to discover that it's empty.
                It would make a nice addition to your campsite.

                You decide to bring it back to your campsite.
            </text>
            <text name="b">
                <b>You now have <output>num2Text(inventory.itemStorageDirectGet().length)</output> storage item slots at camp.</b>
            </text>
        </lib>
        <lib name="nails">
            <text name="a">
                While exploring the desert, you find the wreckage of a building.
                Judging from the debris, it's the remains of the library that was destroyed by the fire.

                You circle the wreckage for a good while and you can't seem to find anything to salvage.
                Until something shiny catches your eye.  There are exposed nails that look like they can be scavenged.

                You take your hammer out of your toolbox and you spend time extracting straight nails.
                Some of the nails you've pulled out are bent but some are incredibly in good condition.
                You could use these nails for construction.

            </text>
            <text name="b">
                After spending nearly an hour scavenging, you've managed to extract <output>$extractedNail</output> nails.
            </text>
        </lib>
    </lib>
    <!-- This encounter is not present in the code and added through xml only -->
    <encounter name="walk">
        <lib name="ss">
            <string name="intro">You walk through the shifting sands for an hour, finding nothing. </string>
            <string name="str">The effort of struggling with the uncertain footing has made you stronger.</string>
            <string name="tou">The effort of struggling with the uncertain footing has made you tougher.</string>
        </lib>
        <!-- logic -->
        <display ref="ss/intro"/>
        <if test="rand(2)==0">
            <if test="rand(2)==0 and player.str lt 50">
                <display ref="ss/str"/>
                <dynStats str="0.5"/>
                <elseif test="player.tou lt 50">
                    <display ref="ss/tou"/>
                    <dynStats tou="0.5"/>
                </elseif>
            </if>
        </if>
    </encounter>
</extend-zone>