<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<story name="celess" xmlns="xxc-story">
	<lib name="strings">
		<lib name="birth">
			<text name="intro">
				You suddenly lose all strength from the waist down, forcing you to lay down on the moss as you go into labor. 

				Unlike what you know of pregnancy, you don’t feel any pain from this, your daughter leaves your womb without trouble and, somehow, you even get an orgasm out of the deal. It starts with the head, then the torso. So far one would think you are giving birth to a human baby, but you know it’s otherwise. A horse body indeed follows suit right after, causing you to orgasm again as white fluids gush out of your happy love canal in a steady flow. She is finally out and starts her life as any and all babies do… with a lengthy and healthy cry!

				You cradle your newborn daughter and bring her to your [breasts], feeling like taking a nap next to your child. First, however, comes an important question.. what will you name her?
			</text>
			<text name="nameScene">
				<i>“<output>$name</output>... this is a good name, right my child?”\n\n</i>
				
				<output>$name</output> stops crying and looks at you with her big eyes, letting out a cute laugh in response.
				You think she likes it. Having solved this important matter, you drift asleep with <output>$name</output> still hugging your chest.
				
				When you wake up, you're no longer holding a baby, but what looks like a centaur girl in her tender years.
				You are hardly surprised, already knowing how short most pregnancies are in Mareth.
				<if test="player.inte gt 50">Maybe it’s due to how time and space distort here?</if>
				Still, you had hoped this phase would have lasted at least a little bit longer.
				<if test="$isCorrupt">
					Your daughter wakes up as well, opening her beautiful crimson eyes to the world.
					She has silver hair and twilight black fur.
					<else>
						Your daughter wakes up as well, opening her beautiful azure eyes to the world.
						She has platinum blonde hair and white fur as befits an unicorn. 
					</else>
				</if>
				You expected her to have grown her horns by now, but strangely enough, her forehead is still clear, perhaps unicorns grow their horns when they grow older?
				[if(intelligence> 50)Does make sense, otherwise they would cause some nasty internal damage during birth.]
				
				<i>“Mom, is something wrong?”</i>
				
				You reply that no… Although you wistfully hope she will stay cute like this forever, despite knowing perfectly well that she will not.
				While you would like to spend more time enjoying your role as a parent you still have a lot of things to do, so you simply tell her to stay at camp for now whenever you're not here for her safety.
			</text>
		</lib>
		<text name="growUp">
			As you wake up this morning, you check the space next to you where <output>$name</output> usually sleeps, and find it empty. 
			You almost panic for a moment, before calming down and deciding to go look for her. 
			When you finally find her by the stream, she’s holding her forehead, visibly in pain.
			
			<if test="$isCorrupt">
				<i>“Ahhhh so good… this feels way too good!…Mom please look!”</i>
				
				Well, looks like it wasn’t pain, not at all. You watch spellbound as a duo of parallel horns, symbols of her corruption, push out of <output>$name</output>’s forehead. 
				She holds her horns like a pair of dicks, playing her hands along their length as if trying to masturbate them. 
				Speaking of which, her 25 inch long horse cock is now fully erect and throbbing, almost as if an invisible hand was toying with it, a thick flow of precum steadily seeping out already.
				Her breasts, currently D-cups, are progressively inflating, finally stopping somewhere around E-cups. And as her horns finish their growth, her horsecock explodes, splattering much of the ground, covering it in white.
				Your little girl seems to have matured to adulthood.
				
				<i>“Mom… I feel so energised, and hot... please... help me get that throbbing thing to calm down.”</i>
				<display ref="../incest/doHeatOrRut"/>
				<else>
					<i>“Oww! It hurts!...Mom… don’t look!”</i>
					
					You see your daughter is holding a large horns on her forehead. It seems she finally reached adulthood, her breasts inflating to E-cups only confirms your suspicion. She seems to be in pain
					<if test="silly()">, kinda obvious, what with her outright telling you less than two seconds ago,</if>
					and it’s your duty as her mother to do all you can to help her. You hug her, trying your best to comfort and distract her from the pain as the horns pushes forward, eventually growing to a length just shy of her sire’s own horns.
					
					<i>“Mom… It’s terrible! I've grown this weird bony stump on my head, what do I do?”</i>
					
					You explain to your daughter that it's normal for unicorns to have a horns on their forehead and that you love her all the same, horns or not.
					She calms down and hugs you warmly like she always does. This time, however, you can’t help but notice the large horsecock between her leg rising to full mast.
					Noticing where you’re looking, she blushes and tries to hide it from you, failing miserably due to being unable to reach it with her hands. All she achieves is looking somewhat silly.
					You tell her it’s alright , that you’re here for her and that, as you already said, you love her, horns or no horns, no matter what kind. This manages to get a chuckle out of her, easing some of her worry, but not all of it.
					You sigh, she’s your daughter, and no matter the problems she might have, she can always come to you and you will gladly go to any length to help her with it. No exceptions.. 
					
					<i>“Mom, I’m a little scared…why did it get so big?! How do I get rid of this huge thing between my legs?”</i>
					
				</else>
			</if>
			
			<if test="player.isFemaleOrHerm()">
				This is a… somewhat unusual situation, but as a <if test="player.isFemale()">female<else>herm like her</else></if> it’s something you can understand.
				<else>You really would prefer not to do this but sadly you have no other way to solve this problem.</else>
			</if>
			You approach your girl’s massive tool and give it a few experimental strokes, making <output>$name</output> gasp in surprise. 
			You lick the flared tip to get a taste, satisfied with it you then proceed to put the thing in your mouth proper. <output>$name</output> moans as her horse dong throbs in appreciation for the attention you’re giving it.
			You suck on her cock until she finally orgasms, the sweet cum flooding your throat.
			
			<if test="$isCorrupt">
				Weirdly enough, you feel something change in you as the corrupted cum reaches your stomach. 
				<else>
					Her cum somehow makes your mind feel clearer and sharper, purifying some of the darker thoughts plaguing you. <output>$name</output>’s horsecock finally shrinks back to its sheath, but she’s still blushing like a tomato.
					
					<i>“Mom, is this really ok with you?”</i>
					
					You would rather it be you than some imp after her purity, stealing your daughter firsts. 
					She understands you’re doing this for her sake and does her best to stop blushing, being only moderately successful. 
					The morning pretty much continues as normal, aside from a lecture on sex you put some time aside to give her, mainly on what and who to avoid and why.
				</else>
			</if>
			
		</text>
		<lib name="incest">
			<text name="masturbateHer">
				You simply help her by masturbating her horse dong to satisfaction. <output>$name</output> thanks you afterward and goes to sit in a corner to rest.
			</text>
			<text name="centaurToys">
				You point at the centaur toys and she swiftly gallops to them with a clear idea of how to use them.
				Well that's one problem solved.
			</text>

			<text name="pureCorruption">
				<output>$name</output> suddenly starts moaning as she holds her horns with both hands.
				
				<i>“Ahhhh so good… this feels way too good!…Mom, please look!”</i>
				
				You watch spellbound as her horns suddenly fissures by the center, dividing into a duo of parallel horns, symbol of her newfound corruption.
				Her formerly pure white fur starts to darken to pitch black as her eyes’ irises lose their azure blue, changing shade towards a fiendish red. Even her hairs changes silks of silver replacing her former platinum blonde strands. 
				She holds her horns like a pair of dicks, playing her hands along their length as if trying to masturbate them. 
				Speaking of which, her 25 inch long horse cock is now fully erect and throbbing, almost as if an invisible hand was toying with it, a thick flow of precum steadily seeping out already. 
				And as her horns finish repositioning on each side of her forehead, her horsecock explodes, splattering much of the ground, covering it in white. <output>$name</output> seems to have embraced her inner corruption.
				
				<i>“Mom… I feel so energised, and hot... please... help me get that throbbing thing to calm down.”</i>
				
				This is a… somewhat unusual situation, but it’s something you can understand.
				You approach your girl’s massive tool and give it a few experimental strokes, making <output>$name</output> gasp in surprise. 
				You lick the flared tip to get a taste. Satisfied with it you then proceed to put the thing in your mouth proper. <output>$name</output> moans as her horse dong throbs in appreciation for the attention you’re giving it. 
				You suck on her cock until she finally orgasms, the sweet cum flooding your throat.
				
				Weirdly enough, you feel something change in you as the corrupted cum reaches your stomach. 
			</text>
			
			<text name="corruptMenu">
				You ask <output>$name</output> if she’s up for some ‘fun’ with her mommy. <output>$name</output>’s horse ears instantly perk up at the mere mention of “fun”.

				<i>“How would you like us to do it?”</i>
			</text>
			
			<text name="fuckHer">
				It’s not everyday you get to see a centauress with such a fine pussy<if test="player.hasStatusEffect(StatusEffects.TelAdre) eq true">beside Edryn's of course</if>.
				You ponder for a split second the implications of what you’re about to do, it’s about how long it takes you to dismiss them.
				Amongst all of the people you know, the only one even remotely likely of still being a virgin is your daughter and with the way she debauches herself on a daily basis using the natural fauna
				<if test="player.hasKeyItem('Fake Mare') ge 0 || player.hasKeyItem('Centaur Pole') ge 0"> or the toys you brought back from Whitney’s farm</if>
				, you’re pretty sure her innocence died out a long time ago. <output>$name</output> is a big girl with… equally big assets, but today what you’re interested in is her gaping horsecunt.
				<if test="silly()">You monster.</if>When you mention it to her, she doesn't even seem surprised, aside from asking what took you so long.
				Merely smiling while teasingly flaunting her moistening cunt toward you, taunting you to take her already.
				
				<i>“Mommy wanna play daddy today? Sure, I can get in front of that ride.”</i>
				
				That being all the encouragement you need, you position yourself behind her and ram  your [cock] into her warm gaping cunt without hesitation.
				She moans in delight as you force in as much of your cock as you can while looking for the perfect angle. <output>$name</output> taunts you with dirty talk all the while.
				
				<i>“Mom, please defile me as much as you want, punish my sinful pussy!”</i>
				
				Sinful, eh? Like mother like daughter. Her pussy, despite its size, acts as if it had a mind of its own, squeezing your cock as if trying to smother it.
				You would suspect her of having some succubus blood were you not aware of her actual heritage.
				
				<i>“Tired already, mom? C’mon, you can screw me better than that! Or, perhaps, you'd rather be the one to be screwed?” </i>
				
				Oh, is that a little brat mocking you that you hear? Can’t have that, right? Let’s educate her!
				You proceed to wildly fuck your nymphomaniac daughter’s hole, responding to her earlier assault with a flurry of aggressive thrusts. 
				
				<i>“Aaaaah Yes! Defile me! Use me to your heart's content!”</i>
				
				In the end, you manage to outlast her. With a scream, you orgasm, a handful of seconds after she does. You flood her thirsty cunt with your cum, making her moan in delight.
				As expected, nothing spills out of her pussy, even after the both of you lay down in the grass to rest. 
				
				You snuggle for a time with <output>$name</output> then head back to your daily routine.
				<display ref="../doHeatOrRut"/>
			</text>
			<text name="suckHerOff">
				It's been a while since you last had a taste of her, thus you decide to give your daughter a sweet, loving blowjob! <output>$name</output> coos, delighted at the proposal.
				
				<i>“Oh… so mommy wants a taste of my delicious lower horns? Please, mom, feel free to indulge yourself.”</i>
				
				You approach your girl’s massive tool and give it a few experimental strokes, making <output>$name</output> gasp in surprise.
				You lick the flared tip to get a taste.
				Satisfied with it you then proceed to put the thing in your mouth proper. <output>$name</output> moans as her horse dong throbs in appreciation for the attention you’re giving it. 
				You suck on her cock until she finally orgasms, the sweet cum flooding your throat.
				
				Weirdly enough, you feel something change in you as the corrupted cum reaches your stomach.
				<display ref="../doHeatOrRut"/>
			</text>
			<text name="getFucked">
				You could really use some of that horse meat down there and if <output>$name</output>’s raging erection is anything to go by, she’s in line with your thinking.
				
				You get rid of any clothing, giving a good show of your [ass] to <output>$name</output> who blushes in desire while trotting up to you. Soon, you feel the tip of her huge cock at the entrance of your vagina.
				
				<i>“Here I go, mom!” </i>
				
				She’s suddenly inside your pussy before you even had the time to shout a silent scream.
				Weirdly it doesn’t hurt… you’d expect her massive cock to pierce your hymen, yet you don't feel any pain, only the pressure of her large member working your pussy with masterful effectiveness.
				You moan in delight as she fucks you up to the cervix for several minutes, your belly bulging due to the sheer size of her cock.
				Your eyes roll back as her cock drives your pussy completely crazy.. Hell, she has even more stamina than her sire! After a while, you feel her massive shaft twitch inside you as she readies to unload.
				
				<i>“Ahhhh mom.. I can’t hold it anymore!”</i>
				
				A huge volume of cum shoots into you, filling your womb until it’s full enough to make you look pregnant already.
				You feel her removing her cock from your pussy as you pass out on the grass exhausted by the experience. 
				
				When you wake up you find <output>$name</output> sleeping with her head on your lap… seemingly protecting your inflated belly.
				<if test="player.hasVirginVagina()">
					Checking on your privates, you’re not surprised to discover you did, indeed, keep your virginity in spite of the crazy ride the young centauress gave you.
					By now you already figured this is a common thing among unicorns.
				</if>
				You feel something change in you as the corrupted cum reaches your womb.
				<display ref="../doHeatOrRut"/>
			</text>
			<text name="doHeatOrRut">
				Lewd images of cocks <if test="player.isMaleOrHerm()">and vaginas</if> of all sizes and shapes fill your mind, making you drool in anticipation.
				It seems your daughter’s condition is spreading over to you.
				<if test="player.goIntoHeat(true,10)">
					<elseif test="player.goIntoRut(true,10)"/>
				</if>
			</text>
		</lib>
		<text name="campInteraction">
			<output>$name</output> sees you coming over from afar and cheer up right away.
			
			<i>“Mom did you came over to see me?!”</i>
		</text>
		<text name="appearance">
			Your daughter <output>$name</output> is a 
			<if test="$isCorrupt">
				bicorn with 
				abyssal black fur. 
				Her red eyes shine with a glimmer of sinister mischief and depravity, you sometime ponder whether or not she is the spawn of a demon rather than you. Her hairs are silver.
				She wanders around in a black dress. By the look of it you'd think she stole it from a nun of the church of the fetish as it emphasise her generous 
				<if test="$isAdult">
					E
					<else>
						D
					</else>
				</if>
				 cup breast and put the focus on her assets. 
				
				<else>
					unicorn with 
					immaculate white fur.
					Her blue eyes are the most innocent you've seen on mareth, if angels did exist she would be one. Her hairs are platinum blonde.
					She wander around in a white dress that covers her more than decent 
					<if test="$isAdult">
						E
						<else>
							D
						</else>
					</if>
					 cup breasts, through where she found it is a mystery even to you. Maybe it was a gift from her father though he never shown back to reclaim her.
					
				</else>
			</if> 
			
			<output>$name</output> inherited a massive horsecock from her father. Easily 
			<if test="$isAdult">
				20
				<else>
					10
				</else>
			</if>
			 inch long, this beast can apparently, if the tales are true, pierce through anything.
			
			<if test="$isCorrupt">
				She regularly use it to fuck imps and goblins alike when she is horny.
				
				<else>
					She tend to be afraid of it, still too young and pure to understand how to properly use it. 
					
				</else>
			</if>
			Just like all centauresses <output>$name</output> has a horse vagina behind her hindquarter.
			<if test="$isCorrupt">
				Knowing her well she likely already took enough cock down that way to beat a succubus at the art of fucking. Your lascivious daughter is far from virgin.
				<else>
					You pray that she will not lose her virginity to some corrupt creature. It will be your duty as a parent to preserve her innocence for as long as possible in this messed up world.
				</else>
			</if>
		</text>
		<lib name="itemImprove">
			<text name="menuText">It occurs to you that <output>$name</output> could use her powers to empower one of your items, potentially creating powerful artifacts. Which item do you want to reforge?</text>
			<text name="improveThatItem">
				You ask <output>$name</output> if she could imbue an item with her power.
				
				<i>“Certainly mother! Just leave the item on the ground and let me get to work.”</i>
				
				<output>$name</output> trots over to the item and starts channeling power. 
				<if test="$isCorrupt">
					You see her twin horns blazing with a dark purple aura of corruption as her horse cock goes erect. 
					She start to massage her breasts then moans, her eyes rolling out as she spontaneously orgasms, a river of black cum flooding out of her flare right unto the item.
					You see the armament transforming as fluid corruption seeps into the material, infusing it with unholy power. 
					
					She sighs in relief, shakes out the few last drops of corrupt cum, then steps away, leaving you to examine the fruit of her work.
					<else>
						Her horns starts to glow with a white halo of purity.
						She cradles the item within her hands like a newborn baby, then finally touches it with her horns, transferring the light into it.
						A miracle happens, as the item changes shape and starts to glow with holy power.
						
						Finally done, she comes back to you and solemnly deposits the blessed armament in your hand.
					</else>
				</if>
			</text>
		</lib>
		<lib name="forest-unicorn">
			<lib name="intro">
				<text name="intro">
					As you wander the woods, you stumble upon a large clearing.
					The place is pure - so pure that the rest of Mareth looks like a corrupted wasteland in comparison, which given the current state of things, isn’t that far from the truth.
					In the center of this natural masterpiece sits a large stone altar, upon which rests a magnificent white shield ornamented with gold filigree.
					As you approach the shield, a powerful wall of force stops you a few feet away from the item.

					<i>“None shall take this sacred relic from this place without my consent!”</i>

					You turn over just in time to see a massive horse-like figure charging at you, barely managing to move out of the way in time to avoid being trampled.
					Your assailant is now standing between you and the altar, letting you get a good view at the grove’s ostensible guardian:

					The woman has silvery white hair flowing around her perfect visage; and her sizable E cup would make most women back in Ingnam green with envy, then again, most things even somewhat female here in Mareth would cause the same reaction.
					The comparison to a human, however, ends there.
					Below her waist is the large lower-body of an immaculate white horse.
					Her ears are covered with silvery white fur and while at first you mistook her for just a centaur warrior, the spear-like spiraling horns on her forehead warns you that there might be more to her.

					<i>“Just leave and I won’t have to attack you. I swear on my honor that I won’t give chase should you leave peacefully. This is for your own good.”</i>
				</text>
				<text name="virgin">
					She suddenly sniffs something in the air and her expression changes to one of baffled disbelief.

					<i>“How is this even still possible in this lost corrupted land? A chaste person on Mareth?!”</i>

					She approaches to examine you thoroughly now. Once satisfied, she declares, <i>“Well I have no idea how you managed it, but you stayed a virgin and pure despite the mess around here.”</i>

					You understand the reason for her surprise, chastity in Mareth is as rare as rain nowadays.
					Your virginity is a testament to your strength, you have fought tooth and nail to protect it, partly due to the values you were taught, mostly due to knowing what most inhabitants of Mareth would do to you once you were defenseless.
					You tell her as much, causing her surprise to turn into respect.
					Having answered her question, you ask one in turn, namely, what is she doing here, exactly?
					You can already see she is some sort of guardian, probably of that shield over there, but you would like to know the specifics.

					<i>“I was tasked with guarding the divine shield, Sanctuary, from dark influence.
						Demons cannot enter this grove and the impure reels at the mere thought of setting a single foot into this area.
						This armament needs a champion to wield it and take the fight to the fiends;
						however, due to Mareth’s purity being compromised, people who match this description have almost all been destroyed by transformations or defiled by the many demonic inhabitants of the land.
						Only a pure maiden such as you can hope to get past the ward.”</i>

					Interested in the magnificent shield on the altar, you ask what you would need to do to get access to this shield, since you already fulfill the requirements for entering here.

					<i>“Simple, since only one carrying my essence can pass the ward, I just need to share my essence with you.”</i>

					You raise an eyebrow at that, you’ve been in Mareth long enough to know an innuendo when you hear one, but surely such a pure individual must have meant something far more innocent.
					Still, you do glance at her lower half to make sure.
					Aaaand of course she has a horsecock, already at half-mast, too.
					You bite down a sigh, you’re in fucking Mareth, of <i>course</i> she has one.
					Your first guess was right, at least.
					That meager consolation does little to numb the disappointment.
				</text>
				<text name="noVirgin">
					You ask her why she is defending this relic and what it would take for you to gain access to it.
					She eyes you as if trying to figure out your intentions then sigh.

					<i>“Only the pure of heart and body may be allowed to pick up this shield, Marae herself tasked me with guarding it.
						If you truly wish to prove your worthiness then I will ask of you that you perform a task for me.”</i>

					What task?

					<i>“In the darkest reaches of the forest lurks a terrifying creature of great corruption known as a nightmare.
						It is anathema to purity and must be disposed of. Slay the nightmare and I will grant you access to the shield.”</i>

					On those word you leave, better seek out this creature as fast as possible.
				</text>
				<text name="introAfterNightmare">
					You manage to find your way back to the sacred grove. As expected the guardian is swift to show, blocking your path to the shield her tall frame acting like a wall.
					
					<i>“Sorry but until you have proven yourself I cannot allow you any further.”</i>
				</text>
				<text name="introAfterNightmareShowProof">
					You pull the nightmare twin horns out of your bag for the unicorn maiden to see, she nods in approval.
					
					<i>“What you did today perhaps will help to save what's left of this beautiful forest. Please allow me to perform this small service for you as a reward. I will restore that which you lost to the ravage of this fallen land.”</i>
					
					Her horn begins to glow a warm soothing light and, as she touches your cheek with her right hand you feel something change in your body as you recover your<if test="player.hasPerk(PerkLib.HistoryWhore)"> long</if> lost virginity. That said what happens now that you are pure again?
					
					<i>“I was tasked with guarding the divine shield, Sanctuary, from dark influence. Demons cannot enter this grove and the impure reels at the mere thought of setting a single foot into this area. This armament needs a champion to wield it and take the fight to the fiends; however, due to Mareth’s purity being compromised,
					people who match this description have almost all been destroyed by transformations or defiled by the many demonic inhabitants of the land. Only a pure virgin person such as you can hope to get past the ward.”</i>
					
					Interested in the magnificent shield on the altar, you ask what you would need to do to get access to this shield, since you already fulfill the requirements for entering here.
					
					<i>“Simple, since only one carrying my essence can pass the ward, I just need to share my essence with you.”</i>
					
					You raise an eyebrow at that, you’ve been in Mareth long enough to know an innuendo when you hear one, but surely such a pure individual must have meant something far more innocent. Still, you do glance at her lower half to make sure. Aaaand of course she has a horsecock, already at half-mast, too.
					You bite down a sigh, you’re in fucking Mareth, of <i>course</i> she has one. Your first guess was right, at least. That meager consolation does little to numb the disappointment.
					
					<i>“So… you want this shield or not?”</i>
				</text>
			</lib>
			<text name="noway">
				You give her the same answer you gave all others, a flat “No” that leaves no room for negotiation
				<if test="silly()">followed by singing <i>“nope, nope, nope, fuck this shit, I’m out!” </i></if>
				as you turn around and leave. You fought hard to keep your virginity, no amount of loot is going to tempt you.
			</text>
			<text name="okay-male">
				You look at her cock, then your rear, then back to her cock.
				<if test="player.inte gt 70">
					You don’t need to be a genius, which you are, to tell that that won’t fit without either injury or magic.
					And since the only ones you know of that have any kind of magic that fits the bill are the Demons, you have your doubts about the later option.
					<else>
						You might not be a genius, but even you know that that won’t fit without injury on your end.
					</else>
				</if>
				You tell her as much.

				<i>“You forget I’m no ordinary centaur. First and foremost please bend over…”</i>

				Well, if that’s what it takes to obtain that unique and likely very powerful shield you guess you will have to. You get on all fours as the looming shadow of the centauress moves right above you. You feel her huge horse cock right up your ass cheek.
				<if test="player.isNaked() eq false">
					Wait didn’t you have your clothes still on? How come she is already at your pucker entrance without removing anything!
					<if test="player.inte gt 70">
						Is she seriously using spatial magic of all things just to avoid the bother of undressing you?
					</if>
				</if>

				<i>“A unicorn ‘horns’ can pierce through anything, just relax it will be easier for you.”</i>
				<if test="silly() and playre.inte gt 70">
					Part of you is mildly surprised, and grateful, no Demon has realized this potential application of spatial magic, otherwise they would have pushed to develop it until they learnt how to open portals to other realms by ramming a dick against space-time until they fucked it into submission.
				</if>

				Without warning she suddenly shoves her huge horsecock inside, stretching your ass wide!
				As expected it hurts a fair bit, but eventually pain recedes as you acclimate to it.
				Or are you truly? The pain is slowly turning to pleasure as you start moaning, your [if(isMale)cock|crotch] becoming extremely sensitive.
				[if(isMale)You cum once then twice as it starts to shrink,|Your body starts to change,]
				your moans becoming progressively less and less masculine until they sound just like those of a girl. Wait a girl?

				<i>“Ahhhn I can’t hold myself! Take it all”</i>

				As she cums into your ass you feel
				[if(isMale)what’s left of your cock and balls continue shrinking inside of you until all that’s left is a slit|
				yourself becoming increasingly feminine up to the point a slit appear where used to be nothing up your crotch].
				While you were concerned about your [if (isMale) cock|new feminine assets] you didn’t notice your chest had changed too, now you're sporting a pair of [breasts]!

				Wait... what the hell!? Did she just change you into a girl?! This wasn’t part of the agreement!

				<i>“We ain’t done yet… here comes part two.”</i>

				You see her looming shadow above your crouched female form, her horse length already hard again. Well, shit.
			</text>
			<text name="okay-female">
				<lib name="str">
					<text name="taurIntro">
						Well now that she mention it you must admit you indeed have been eyeing her fat horsemeat for a fair while now.
						Being a centaur makes it difficult for you to find relief especially since you decided not to relinquish your virginity.
						You smirk seductively giving her a fair view of your virgin equine pussy as you tell the unicorn that for your first time, you might as well take a stallion.
						Your pussy lips are already wet in anticipation of her maleness.\n
					</text>
					<text name="intro"><i>“Well, since you agreed, I will let you in on a little secret. I won’t need to take your virginity. Rather, my ‘horns’ will pierce right through it.”\n\n</i></text>
					<text name="taurSex">
						She trots to you, her massive horsemeat hardening as she prepares to mount your [pussy]. She take a whiff of your [pussy] going so far as to give it a lick or two just so she can taste it. Satisfied, she gets on you and you can feel the tip of her flare making contact with your vaginal lips.

						<i>“Mmmmmm what a nice mare pussy. I can only imagine how it will feel to fuck that. Well, here I go!” </i>

						You neigh in surprise as she suddenly slides her entire length inside your pussy.
						Weirdly, it doesn’t hurt… you’d expect her massive cock to pierce your hymen yet you don't feel any pain, only the pressure of her large member working your pussy with masterful effectiveness.
						You moan and neigh in delight as she fucks you for several minutes, her horsecock filling your equine pussy like no other.
						Your eyes roll back as her cock drives your [pussy] completely crazy hitting every single sensitive spot in your massive horsecunt.
						The unicorn is not faring any better, drooling as she fucks your [pussy] silly.
						You can only guess that she doesn't get to fuck a mare this often.\n
					</text>
					<text name="sex">
						It’s too late to say no now and you decide to bend over <if test="$wasMale">again</if> for the centauress. Soon you feel her huge horse meat making contact with your walls entrance
						<if test="player.isNaked() eq false and $wasMale ne true">which is weird because you were quite sure you still had your clothes on.

						</if>

						<i>“Here I go!”</i>

						She’s suddenly inside your pussy before you even had the time to shout a silent scream.
						<if test="$wasMale">
							As with your ass just a moment ago, she doesn’t cause you any pain due to her size, nor does she break your hymen. You do feel the pressure of her large member working your pussy with masterful effectiveness though.
							<else>
								Weirdly, it doesn’t hurt… you’d expect her massive cock to pierce your hymen yet you don't feel any pain, only the pressure of her large member working your pussy with masterful effectiveness.
							</else>
						</if>
						You moan in delight as she fucks you up to the cervix for several minutes, your belly bulging due to the sheer size of her cock. Your eyes roll back as her cock drives your pussy completely crazy\n
					</text>
					<text name="outro">
						<i>“Ahhhh! I can’t hold it anymore!”</i>

						A huge volume of cum shoots into you, filling your womb until it’s full enough to make <if test="$isTaur">your lower body<else>you</else></if> look pregnant already.
						You feel her removing her cock from your pussy as you <if test="$isTaur">
						lie down on the ground to rest exhausted by the experience.
						<else>
							pass out on the grass exhausted by the experience.
						</else>
					</if>

						When you wake up you are no longer in the grove.
						It would seem that the unicorn moved you to the forest’s edge.
						She did keep her word, however, since the fabled shield is resting on your lap… seemingly protecting your inflated<if test="$isTaur"> horse</if> belly.
						<if test="$isTaur">
							You feel that all of her cum is still inside of you, somehow kept from leaking out and sloshing as you move.
							<else>
								Checking on your privates, you’re surprised to discover that your virginity is indeed intact despite the crazy ride the centauress gave you.
								Heck, all of her cum is still inside of you, somehow kept from leaking out and sloshing as you move.
							</else>
						</if>

						You head back to camp, still confused with this experience.\n\n
					</text>
				</lib>
				<if test="$isTaur and $wasMale ne true">
					<display ref="str/taurIntro"/>
				</if>
				<display ref="str/intro"/>
				<if test="$isTaur and $wasMale ne true">
					<display ref="str/taurSex"/>
					<else>
						<display ref="str/sex"/>
					</else>
				</if>
				<display ref="str/outro"/>

			</text>
			<text name="fuck-her">
				It’s not everyday you get to see a centauress with such a fine pussy<if test="player.hasStatusEffect(StatusEffects.TelAdre) eq true"> beside Edryn's of course</if>.
				You ask the unicorn about it.

				<i>“Umph... I guess that can work too, but I'm only doing it because you are a virgin, unicorns don’t mate with anything else.”</i>

				That being all the encouragement you need, you position yourself behind her to insert your [cock] into her warm, gaping cunt.
				She moans in delight as you push as much of your cock as you can inside, still looking for the perfect angle.
				The unicorn taunts you all the while.

				<i>“Pah! You should be grateful I’m even allowing you! With the demonic plague, the unicorn population has been decreasing dramatically.
					As such, it’s  my responsibility to increase it, so you better not waste my virginity, you sinner.”</i>

				Sinner, eh? We'll see about sins later. Her pussy is quite large, so you have to work double time to make her feel anything at all.
				You proceed to wildly fuck the unicorn’s hole with aggressive thrusts in order to, at the very least, make her moan.
				You eventually reach your limit and flood her cunt with your cum, making her whine.
				You check the results, but to your surprise not only nothing spills out of her cunt, but her hymen is actually still intact!

				<i>“I guess that will have to do… you can have the shield. Now get out of here, I have a pregnancy to manage.”\n\n</i>
			</text>
			<text name="armorScene">
				You stumble upon the forest grove where the shield used to be.
				The unicorn has long left but you spot a shine on the ground deeper in.
				It looks like a set of untarnished silvery armor, likely an ancient treasure she left.
				Upon unearthing the piece, you discover this full plate armor was clearly not made for a human but a centaur.

				The breastplate is ornamented with what you assume is a holy symbol, namely a blossoming oak tree <if test="flags[kFLAGS.MET_MARAE] gt 0">obviously Marae’s</if>.
				It has plated barding and a skirt fit for a horse  body, it even comes with matching horseshoes.
				While clearly made like a full plate, it is surprisingly flexible, allowing for maneuverability similar to that of light armor, which is rather unusual.

			</text>
		</lib>
	</lib>
</story>