<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!--TODO @Oxdeception convert strings to XXC XML-->
<story name="diva" xmlns="xxc-story">
    <lib name="combat">
        <lib name="moves">
            <lib name="embrace">
                <text name="hit">
                    Diva suddenly dives and closes her wings and arms on you, locking you in an embrace!
                    <if test="silly()">Bad touch, bad touch!</if>
                </text>
                <text name="miss">
                    Diva suddenly dives and attempt to closes her wings and arms on you but you're faster than her and swiftly evade the grapple.
                </text>
            </lib>
            <text name="bite">
                Diva bites into your neck and begins drinking her fill. The rather loud slurping noises she makes kind of ruin the mood, though. Weirdly enough you feel aroused from this despite the pain.
                <if test="silly()">You masochist, you.</if>
            </text>
            <text name="biteGargoyle">
                Diva tries to bite you but quickly step back holding a hand to her mouth with a surprised yelp of clear pain. You smirk amused... did she seriously try to bite in your stone skin?
            </text>
            <text name="bitePlant">
                Diva tries to bite you but just as her fang pierce her skin she shove you off and start spitting.

				<i>
                    “Puaaah what the hell did I taste just now! Your blood taste like saps and flower nectar. How disgusting!”

                </i>
                Well now you're kind of offended by her reaction... guess plant sap really tastes bad for her.
            </text>
            <text name="swoopToss">
                Diva makes a pass bare inches above your head, using her momentum to snatch
                <if test="$final">
                    and toss you across the room and into an intimate reunion between your face and the wall.
                    <else>you only to drop you from higher height.</else>
                </if>
            </text>
            <lib name="darkness">
                <text name="cast">
                    <i>
                        “Let us see how thou fight without this precious light of yours!”

                    </i>
                    Diva lands, opening her wings wide as a pair of black orbs form at her fingertips.
                    She shatter them on the ground plunging the room in complete darkness and extinguishing all light.
                    You will be unable to locate her correctly without a proper visual.
                </text>
                <text name="dispell">
                    the room light back as the flame dispels the shadow.
                </text>
            </lib>
            <text name="sonicScream">
                <if test="$final">
                    Diva suddenly lets out an agonising screech which echoes through the entire room, shattering all the glass along it’s path and forcing you to reflexively try to cover your ears with your hands, dropping your weapons in the process and still staggering you despite your efforts.
                    The scream is so powerful that, in addition to damaging your eardrums and fucking your balance something fierce, it also bodily throws you into a nearby wall.
                    At least you didn’t wind up impaled on some weapon’s rack, that would be plain embarrassing.
                    <else>
                        Diva gets what look like a conical item out of her bag and suddenly lets out an agonising screech which echoes through the entire room, forcing you to reflexively try to cover your ears with your hands, dropping your weapons in the process and still staggering you despite your efforts.
                    </else>
                </if>
            </text>
        </lib>
        <lib name="scenes">
            <text name="blinded">
                Diva recoils in pain as the bright light strike her like a hammer, temporarily pinning her to the ground and stunning her.
            </text>
            <lib name="intro">
                <text name="first">
                    You are taking a walk through the mountain area when, much to your annoyance, a thunderstorm begins.
                    However unlike the ones you hear of back home... This thunderstorm has no rain.. peculiar.
                    Ever since you shut down the factory the weather has been erratic switching from clear to a full fledged thunderstorm randomly.
                    Deciding not to head back to camp yet, more out of spite than anything else, you seek shelter instead.
                    Your efforts are rewarded when you spot a large abandoned castle atop a particularly steep hill.
                    Thankfully, it’s not so steep as to require climbing, since the regular lightning bolt would have made that a rather dangerous task what with the risk of a rocky avalanche!
                    As is, you manage to make your way to the front gate without much effort, at least not when compared to some of the climbs you had to do on occasion while exploring this zone.
                    The aforementioned massive wooden doors opening to reveal a rather large vestibule, fitting for a castle this size, you guess.
                    Sadly, there’s no lighting.
                    While you were expecting as much, since the castle did look abandoned and thus has probably been looted down to the bedrock already, it’s still a bother.
                    At least the chances of demons being here has gone down considerably, since it’s unlikely one powerful enough to have gotten themselves night-vision worth a damn would stoop so low as to make their residence look abandoned just to get a cheap shot in.
                    Something else with night vision making this their home, however, still remains a distinct possibility. So either spiders or bats, probably.

                    The gate should make a good choke point, so you pick some debris as silently as you can and get back there, leaving it in a small pile by your side.
                    You unsheathe your weapons, square your shoulders and enter a combat-ready stance, that done, you pick from the little pile of debris whatever looks like it will make the most noise.
                    A metal scrap rusted beyond recognition will do nicely. Your pick made, you proceed to throw it as hard and far as you can into the castle’s depths, ready for anything to jump at you.
                    Nothing does jump out, which scratches out the possibility of anything feral living here, at least on this part of the castle.
                    Sadly, with all the noise the rain is making something could have been startled and, so long as it was far away enough, you wouldn’t have heard it, and since nothing charged at you, it means that if that’s the case it’s either an ambush or someone hiding.
                    With an annoyed sigh you move deeper into the castle, keeping an eye on your back and repeating the same tactic you used at the gate to check for possible traps or ambushes.
                    As you go deeper, you start noticing something moving on the edges of your peripheral vision every now and then, which coupled with the feeling of being watched makes you increasingly paranoid.
                    The fact that whatever or whoever it is makes no noise, or none that you can hear above the rain’s, doesn’t put you at ease, either.
                    You eventually find yourself in what you assume was used as a ball room.
                    As you move to the other end of it to check for anything worthwhile to loot (while you assume everything here has already been looted, you’ll be stuck here until the rain eases, so you might as well), when the door suddenly slams shut behind you, followed by the familiar click of a lock.
                    Between you and the door stands an odd woman, sporting a large leathery cape which covers her entire body.
                    What little you can see of her looks surprisingly human, with her pointy ears being the single exception, then again, you have seen more than one demon use capes like that to “flash” others with their assets, so what she has under her neck is anyone’s guess.
                    Her smile reveals a pair of sharp canines as she announces her intentions.

                    <i>
                        “Fufufufu… foolish mortal! Thou hast walked into mine trap! Abandon all hope of escaping mine castle unscathed, for I am Diva, grand Countess of Dusk!
                        <if test="silly()">You were expecting Dio, but it was I, Diva! </if>
                        Prepare to forfeit thine blood and body to me! TREMBLE BEFORE MINE POWER!”

                    </i>
                    She opens her cape, or rather, her pair of very large bat wings and makes what you assume she thinks is a dramatic leap, diving toward you.
                </text>
                <text name="second">
                    It doesn’t take long before a thunderstorm, yet again, begins.
                    If anyone had told you shutting down the factory would fuck up the weather this much, you would have had second thoughts before taking a wrench to that contol panel.
                    Granted, you would probably have done so anyways, that fucking hellhole deserved no less.
                    Anyhow, knowing the drill already, you march your ass back to Diva’s castle.
                    No sooner you enter that you can already feel movement on the edges of your peripheral vision.
                    Diva is already stalking you, it seems.
                    For one so arrogant and attention hungry, she sure is good at stealth.
                    However, as you expected, the power of drama compels her, so she won’t be showing up until you get somewhere suitable for a dramatic fight.
                    You steel your resolve and push down your exasperation as you decide to just bite the bullet and head to the ball room already, otherwise she will just keep staring at your back from shadowed corners like a lovestruck, socially awkward village girl for hours on end.
                    <if test="silly()">Huh, you might be onto something. Is this that “chuunibyou” thing the mechanic at the factory kept raving on about? He also said something about “Senpais” noticing things and some creature called “tsundere”.</if>

                    Just as you get inside, a triggering mechanism makes itself known, as the doors lock themselves with a click.
                    Huh, she got up to some tinkering between visits, it seems. Neat.
                    You might ask her about how she pulled off that automatic lock trick after you finish the fight <if test="$cabinBuilt">, would be nice to have in your cabin</if>.
                    Diva, unwitting of your musings, appears in a cloud of smoke at the center of the room.
                    special effects, too. You would give a polite clap if you didn’t know she would bitch at you for breaking the mood.

                    <i>
                        “Fufufu... thine foolishness knows no bounds, coming yet again to try and defeat the almighty Countess of Dusk.
                        Dost thou not comprehend such thing is an exercise in futility?
                        No matter, I shall vanquish thee once again and take thy blood and body as mine, hero!
                        Prepare for thy demise!”

                    </i>
                    It takes all of your willpower to keep your palm from having an intimate reunion with it’s lover, your face.
                    Let’s get this over with before you accidentally sigh and hurt her feelings.

                </text>
                <text name="final">
                    This time you don’t even wait for a thunderstorm, you just head straight to Diva’s castle for another match.
                    Truth be told, you are beginning to get endeared to her, somewhat.
                    Not doing anything particularly distasteful to you when she defeated you for the first time certainly won her some points with you.
                    Also, you don’t begrudge having a good sparring partner, it’s nice having someone strong to practice against without any real risks should you lose.

                    Since there's no storm, Diva can’t really sneak around as easily, since there is no thunder to drown out the sound of her movement, so for once you will have to find her yourself.
                    It takes you about three seconds to guess that she will probably be cooped up in the highest tower of the castle.
                    The boarded windows are a bit of a give away, to be honest.
                    Now the question is whether she will be sleeping or waiting for you while sitting in the single gaudiest chair on the whole castle.
                    You eventually reach a room approaching whose gaudiness is nearing critical mass, everything is covered in red and gold, the drapes, the carpet, the coffin and even the fuckhuge throne Diva is sitting in.
                    Unsurprisingly, your guess was right.
                    What you didn’t expect, however is the deer-in-headlights look she is giving you.
                    In that very moment you decide that you are going to learn, or make from scratch if you must, a spell to turn memories into pictures, then fucking frame this moment in the gaudiest frame you find in the castle.

                    <i>“Aaaah...so the prey fancies itself a vampire hunter and dares come up to my very lair to slay me?! Thou shalt be found wanting for I will not go down easily! Prepare thyself, I shall not hold back this time!”</i>

                    And the drama queen fancies herself a dungeon boss, doesn’t she? Seems like either she just keeps away from the sun due to the power of drama compelling her or she is more powerful than you initially thought.

                    <i>“Enough! Cease this foolishness and surrender thine blood and body to me!”</i>

                    She, in what you assume she thinks is an elegant way, throws a glass cup filled with what’s probably blood to the ground as she takes flight, in as much as she can while indoors, high ceilings or not.
                    Aaaaaaand she has gotten herself a battle aura of darkness, of course she has.
                    <if test="silly()">Such is life in the zon- Mareth.</if>
                    But seriously, she is clearly stronger now.
                    Well, it seems she is not holding back this time around.
                </text>
            </lib>
            <lib name="defeated">
                <text name="normal">
                    <i>
                        “Wait, that wasn’t in the script! The hero was supposed to lose to the almighty vampire, be bitten, know love, marry, have children…no no no no and NO!”

                    </i>

                    Is she for real... Does she really think this all was an elaborate play with her as the main character of some romance story?

                    She take on an annoyed expression then declares <i>“Cough cough... ahem..Oh how terrible, I the almighty queen of darkness lost to the hero what will happen of me will thy hero rape me and make me his bride by force or will I be left alone in this castle as he/she goes on for a new quest.“

                </i>

                    Tired of her nonsense you decide to give her exactly what she asked for.
                    But the girl screams a spell that clearly doesn’t exist and disappears in a cloud of smoke from what is obviously a smoke bomb leaving one last warning.

                    <i>
                        “I shall have my vengeance hero for I am the immortal invincible night terror Diva and believe me, I shall never be defeated again by the likes of thou!”

                    </i>

                    It’s only when the smoke disappears that you notice a trap door under the carpet where she was standing.
                    When you try to open it you discover it’s locked.
                    You decide to head back to camp before the weird bat woman show up again.

                </text>
                <text name="combatGargPlant">
                    You fall to the ground unable to fight further as Diva declare.

                    <i>“Look I will be honest with thee thou are completely inedible! Do me a favor and get out. I’m not interested into something I can’t drink from.”</i>

                    Well you can’t believe your luck guess you might as well get going.
                </text>
				<lib name="final">
                    <text name="intro">
                        Diva recoils defeated and falls to the ground on her knee.

                        <i>
                            “Thou are strong… defeating me despite the fact I was at my prime.
                            I would please ask mercy from thee for I have been drinking your blood out of love with thou and would like to become yours if thou would allow it.
                            Would thou be my knight/knightess?”

                        </i>
                        Do you declare mutual love?

                    </text>
                    <text name="yesChoice">
                        She's a good girl, despite her excessive love for acting.
                        You decide to bring her with you back to camp declaring your love for her.
                        Diva nods and, still blushing, she gathers a few important item namely a tent and her coffin.
                        You ask her why she's so keen on bringing a coffin with her anyway, can’t she just sleep in a bedroll like everyone else?

                        <i>
                            “Proper lords only sleep in coffins, I would not have it any other way.
                            As for the tent thou may have figured I dislike bright light.”
                        </i>

                        You shrug and just help her carry the heavy thing back to camp <if test="player.str lt 40">although Diva with her unholy strength still do most of the work</if>.
                        She settles not so far from you, under the shade of a dead tree.
                        She sets up the tent then installs the coffin inside.
                        She works all night and by the time she's done dawn is about to break.
                        She yawns, tired.

                        <i>
                            “I bid thee good day for I must rest now.
                            Should thou want to see me just wake me up or call my name after sunset.”
                        </i>

                        On these words she enters the tent and heads to sleep.
                    </text>
                    <text name="noChoice">
                        You will think about it but for now you decide to leave.
                        You guess you will likely need to fight her again and redo her silly play should you want to voice a different choice.
                        In the background you can hear Diva pestering angry about something wrong in the script.
                    </text>
                    <text name="neverChoice">
                        No, you're sick of the games of this bloodsucker.
                        Therefore you decide to leave, heading back to camp and never come back.
                    </text>
                </lib>
            </lib>
        </lib>
        <text name="battleDescript">
            Diva appears to be a vampire, the fangs and wings kind of give it away.
            She circles above and around you, waiting for an opening while she constantly screeches.
            Huh, she might be more bat-like that you initially thought.
            Girl certainly has quite the pair of lungs if nothing else.
            Her red and black dress gives her quite the villainous look, while having some unfortunate consequences what with it having a skirt and she being a flyer.
            Somehow, she manages to keep herself from having a rather intimate reunion with the walls despite not looking at where she is flying in favour of drooling at the sight of your neck.
            Guess all that screeching has an actual purpose aside from annoying you.
            <if test="$final">
                Looks like she got one hell of a power-up thanks to your generous blood donations. Masochism much, Champ?
                <if test="silly()">
                    Git gud, scrub.
                </if>
            </if>
        </text>
    </lib>
    <lib name="camp">
        <lib name="campDescript">
            <text name="day">
                Since it’s daytime Diva is likely sleeping in her coffin.
            </text>
            <text name="evening">
                Diva is quietly doing things next to her tent readying for the night time.
            </text>
            <text name="night">
                Diva is likely hunting a fair the distance away from the camp through you could call her back at any time.
            </text>
        </lib>
        <lib name="campInteraction">
            <text name="dusk">
                Diva is belting a few bottles as she ready up for tonight hunt.
                She notice you by the sound you make before you reach her.

                <i>“Oh hello [name] thou aren’t going to sleep or can’t go to bed yet?”</i>
            </text>
            <text name="night">
                Diva hears your call and flies back to you in a heartbeat.

                <i>
                    “The sun is out it's time to fly out.
                    What about thou [name] would you like to hunt with me or are thou interested into something else?”
                </i>
            </text>
        </lib>
        <lib name="sexMenu">
            <text name="menu">
                <i>“I agree and I’m in the mood for a few exchanges if they are. What thou propose?”</i>
            </text>
            <lib name="moonlightSonata">
                <lib name="intro">
                    <text name="camp">
                        The both of you head back to her castle for a more comfortable bedroom.
                        Once you are sitting on the bed,you two enjoy some idle chat before moving on as Diva close her wings around you in an almost possessive way and bites your neck.
                        Her bite is as pleasurable as ever and you feel at peace with letting her drink your blood.
                        You're not the only one aroused as the vampire clearly seems to also get off on this, looking reder by the second.
                        Diva breaks the embrace, her face red as a tomato as her hand slowly move downward.
                    </text>
                    <text name="combat">
                        You fall to the ground unable to fight further as Diva declares:

                        <i>“Thou have lost, therefore thou have to surrender to me both heart and body. Thy shall pay the blood price first.”</i>

                        Diva close her wings and wrap her arms around you in an almost maternal way, you can feel her E cup breasts press gently against your chest, the temperature between you increasing steadily as she bite in your neck.
                        Her kiss is oddly pleasurable, like a warm bath after a rough day of work and you somehow feel at peace with letting the vampire drink on your blood.
                        You're not the only one aroused however as the pale woman cheeks redden and her eyes droop in a fawning deep love expression.
                        Diva break the embrace, her cheeks as red as the blood that she took, as her hand slowly moves downward.
                    </text>
                </lib>
                <lib name="outro">
                    <text name="camp">
                        As the sun is about to rise, Diva regretfully break the embrace. The two of you back to camp Diva going to her tent.
                        Strangely you don’t feel tired from mating with her all night long.
                    </text>
                    <lib name="combat">
                        <text name="initial">
                            <i>“It’s late and I ought to go before sunrise… thou welcome to come back some time again.”</i>

                            Diva jump off taking flight as she disappears somewhere in a trap door in the roof. You are a little dazed from the blood loss but for some reason you still feel all right. She even left a an item for you.
                        </text>
                        <text name="regular">
                            Diva prepare herself to leave again but gives you a last kiss, making you blush, as the bat girl hand you over what looks like a strange red vial and fly through a hole in the roof.
                        </text>
                    </lib>
                </lib>
                <lib name="male">
                    <text name="regular">
                        Diva slowly start to cup your [balls] then move down to take care of your now raging erection.
                        She start by spitting on your [cock] and stroking it with her hand to properly lube it.
                        You moan as she engulf your tip one of her canine running along your length.
                        She take great care not to bite your cock as she prepares it for later.

                        As It appears, Diva does not favor undergarment which is quite lewd on her part but you're quickly pushed out of your daydreams as she proceed to slide your cock, still covered with drool, out of her mouth.
                        She moves up to you and close both her arms and wings around your body as she get in position.
                        You can feel her cunt right at your [cock] tip.

                        <if test="$combat">
                            <i>“Thou get to taste my second mouth, so thou should feel honored. It's more than you deserve.”</i>
                            <else><i>“Your neck taste good [name] but I will need more than that to be satisfied.”</i></else>
                        </if>

                        Diva slowly slide down on your slick [cock], giving you a fanged smile of bliss as she slowly takes your length in.
                        She feels similar to what you think a succubus would and her pussy clearly has something inhuman about it.
                        She’s now riding you, wings closed around your torso, arms and around your shoulders, as she milks your [cock] thoroughly.
                        You moan in pleasure as the vampire bites your neck in the middle of the act only making you more erect and ready, your [cock] harder than ever.
                        She unplug her mouth if only for a moment just to whisper in your ears.

                        “How does my kiss feels like? Devilish isn’t it? I will bring thou to heaven seven time fold so go ahead and feed both of my mouths, I know thou wants it, so consider thyself to have my permission.”

                        The feeling of her biting you and working your cock is like penetrating and being penetrated at the same time and your eye rolls at the pleasure.
                        Unable to hold any longer, you flood her pussy with your cum
                        <if test="player.cumQ() ge 20">the excess dripping back to the ground </if>,
                        orgasming from both your neck and madly twitching cock.
                        It continue for several hours until sun begins to rise at which point Divah bids you farewell.
                    </text>
                    <text name="tooBig">
                        Diva sees the size of your already erect [cock] and sigh in annoyance.

                        <i>“This thing is unsightly. I think thou will almost thank me for what I will do now.”</i>

                        Diva force you to the ground and you scream as she literally bite your cock!
                        The sharp pain is only temporary however and as blood flow out of your dick you begin to moan from the pleasure forced unto your cock by some sort of aphrodisiac contained in her saliva.
                        You watch stunned both by horror and pleasure as your dick progressively decrease in size down to a more common 18 inch.

                        Diva pulls her lips away from your cock the wound slowly closing.

                        <if test="timesReduced ge 5">
                            <i>“It's the fifth time I have to fix thou art thou seriously enjoying this?”</i>
                            <else><i>“And now for the main course…”</i></else>
                        </if>
                    </text>
                    <text name="bat">
                        You let her bite you first, but it would be unfair if you didn't had your share.
                        You bite her back sharing the blood with her as the two of you do a consanguine exchange.
                        She tastes quite good actually, like a mix of roses and strawberry, and before long you're both red with lust and ready to get down to business as her hand is already at your crotch and is finally reciprocated by yours to her pussy.
                        Both of your necks are bleeding but you don’t care, you are way too focused on getting your respective partner off to do so.
                        Aside from her blood you are quite interested in her other fluids, namely her milk.
                        You move your head to Diva E cup breast and gently start suckling.
                        She moans delighted at your attention holding your head next to her nipples as she nurses you.
                        Her milk is delicious it's a welcome alternative to blood really.
                        Done drinking, you open your mouth with a ‘pop!’, finished with the foreplay as you move on to the main course.
                    </text>
                </lib>
                <lib name="female">
                    <text name="regular">
                        You gasp as her hand tease your already moistening fold.
                        Diva suddenly kisses you.
                        She feeds you a little of your own blood through the kiss and while normally you would find the idea of tasting your own blood a complete turnoff, aroused and messed like you are by the aphrodisiac, it only get’s you even more in the mood.
                        You moan as she starts to slowly finger you, grabbing one of her breasts through her dark dress to return the favor.
                        The vampire girl doesn’t stop you, it seems she’s as aroused as you are.
                        You get under her skirt and insert your fingers in her pussy to return the favor, making her moan in delight.
                        She moves her head to your chest smiling with a lusty gaze as she gently caresses your breast.
                        Strangely the bite from earlier caused them to slowly inflate with milk buildup while you weren't looking.

                        <i>“I think I will take my share here too. Thou can enjoy.”</i>

                        Before you know it, Diva kisses your areola and begins to gently suckle on your left teat.
                        She has experience in this, as not only she nurses from you without effort, but she even manage to avoid piercing your nipples with her sharp canines.
                        The feeling in your chest is delightful and you let the vampire slowly empty you of your milk reserves, her expert hands slowly bringing you to the edge.
                        You decide to help her out to by fingering her under her skirt, making her moan on your breast.

                        The both of you are to busy to notice time passing until suddenly the coming dawn pierce through a window. Her mouth regretfully move away from your chest with a small pop as she breaks away from you.
                    </text>
                    <text name="bat">
                        You let her bite you first but it would be unfair if you didn't had your share.
                        You bite her back sharing the blood with her as the two of you do a consanguine exchange.
                        She tastes quite good actually, like a mix of roses and strawberry, and before long you're both red with lust and ready to get down to business as her hand already in your wet fold is finally reciprocated by yours.
                        Both of your necks are bleeding but you don’t care, you are way too focused on getting your respective partner off to do so.
                        You gasp as her hand tease your already moistening fold.
                        You moan as she starts to slowly finger you, grabbing one of her breasts through her dark dress to return the favor.
                        The vampire girl doesn’t stop you, it seems she’s as aroused as you are.
                        You get under her skirt and insert your fingers in her pussy to return the favor making her moan in delight.
                        Soon the splashes of blood on the ground are mixed with girl cum creating a larger puddle as you orgasm together.
                        Having sex only in a single position would not be enough for you both however and you pull her to the ground as you begin to actively slurp on her pleasure palace.
                        She rewards your attention by doing the same, filling your [pussy] just perfectly with her tongue.
                        However you realise the both of you are still thirsty as she move her head to your chest smiling with a lusty gaze, gently caressing your [breasts]. Of course her bite caused your breast to swiftly inflate with the telltale presence of milk.

                        <i>“Milk is highly nutritious too, I think I will take my share there as well. Thou can enjoy.”</i>

                        Before you know it Diva kisses your areola and begins to gently suckle on your left teat.
                        She has experience in this as not only she nurses from you without effort, but she even manage to avoid piercing your nipples with her sharp canines.
                        The feeling in your chest is delightful but she is not alone here to be hungry so the both of you switch position so you can have access to her shapely E cup breasts and start suckling her.
                        Diva moans in appreciation and grab your other breast with her hand, squeezing and tweaking your nipples to your enjoyment.
                        The two of you are barely getting started as you slide her finger inside her already sopping wet cunt.
                        Diva unplug and smile wide at your interest.

                        <i>“Want to proceed to step three?”</i>

                        Of course you do and fingering her to orgasm will be your pleasure.
                        Diva gasp as you begin to play inside her wet cunt.
                        She however won't leave you unattended for, sliding her fingers straight to your [cunt] in order to equalise the score.
                        You moan appreciative of the attention and begin fingering her in earnest.
                        You both pant in delight as you slowly finger the other to orgasm your clear and sticky fluids splattering on each others hands.
                        Still, even after that, you continue having sex the whole night long.

                        Time passes and the sun start to rise. You step away from the window as she does the same.
                    </text>
                </lib>
            </lib>
            <text name="shareAMeal">
                You offer to share a midnight meal with Diva something the vampire immediately grin to.

                <i>“Thou inviting me to dine tonight? How galant.”</i>

                The both of you move in the darkness that night, looking for an easy meal.
                Not so surprisingly the mountain range is full of minotaurs and a sleeping minotaur is indeed the first thing the pair of you find.
                Diva having more experience than you in that domain close her wings around the minotaur left arm, she takes aim and immediately go for his carotid.
                The bull man wake up but it’s too late for him to resist as Diva’s naturally pleasurable embrace is already soothing him into submission.
                Truth be told the raging boner of his bull cock is enough of a tell for anyone to figure how he feels about having his blood sucked.
                You proceed to settle on his right side biting his large collar for your own food source.
                The pair of you moan in delight at the taste of fresh warm blood flooding your mouth while the minotaur pleasure reach a peak, his cock starting to erupt cum like a fountain.
                Diva, considerate of your unwilling victim, give him a handjob to keep his pleasure growing while she keep sucking more and more of his blood the minotaur hips bucking the air mechanically as his dick escape his control.
                Soon the minotaur eye rolls and he falls unconscious.
                Whether it's from blood loss or from the consecutive orgasm the both of you have been forcefully inflicting on him is unknown.
                Diva and you break out from the embrace for a long coppery kiss, exchanging blood and saliva.

                <i>“Not the highest quality… I prefer yours [name]. Still the feast is better enjoyed with two then alone don’t you think?”</i>

                This carry on for the whole night, the pair of you making love and feasting on numerous consecutive victims at the same time.
                It's only when outside on the prowl that you notice how gracefully and efficiently she hunt at night, her technique both at lovemaking and hunting is simply flawless.
                The both of you head back to camp, highly satiated, as the sun begins to rise again.
                Diva bids you good day as she head to her tent and coffin. As for yourself, you think your job is done when you walk at day so you skip sleep this time around.

                Not so surprisingly, your nightly vampiric meal offset this issue granting you the energy to go without rest this time around.
            </text>
            <text name="bloodyRose">
                You point out to Diva tent and both of you head in.

                Once inside, you give Diva a seductive gaze, offering your neck on display and removing your clothes. The vampire needs no further invitation as she toss hers at the back of her tent. Diva snuggle up to you, kisses your neck and then bite in. The feeling of the blood running out of your neck is a delicious mix of pain and pleasure arousing you to no end. In the delight of the moment you also bite Diva, tasting her blood. It never occurred to you before how powerful the link between the both of you are when feeding from each others neck… were you two any closer than that you would be able to communicate through telepathy. You feel her pleasure through your neck as she can feels yours through her own.. or perhaps you both feels each other pleasure more clearly?

                <if test="player.isMale">
                    Your [cock] begins to harden from the overstimulation of your sensible vampire neck and the excitement of blood.
                    Diva pussy seems to agree as she’s practically wetting the ground below the pair of you.
                    Giving in to your instinct you slowly insert yourself in her like your fang in her neck as your increasingly hardening [cock] begin to pulse along with your heartbeat.
                    Her pussy react similarly to your cock to the penetration, she’s more than ready to go.
                    You both moan in each others neck as you begin to hugfuck her.
                    Diva’s pussy is like a living creature, clenching strongly on your [cock] and pulsing as if to milk you dry.
                    You however aren’t going to simply lay back and let the devilish pussy do all the work as you begin to piston in and out of her.
                    Diva’s wings are flapping wildly behind her <if test="player.wings.type == VAMPIRE">, yours too and you try not to take flight as a the winds created by your combined flapping shake the tent</if>.
                    Both of you scream in ecstasy, breaking out of the bite, blood still dripping from each other chin as you cum your load in her greedy vagina
                    <if test="player.cumQ() ge 20"> the excess dripping to the ground</if>.

                    <elseif test="player.isFemale">
                        You begin to feel more than blood oozing out of you.
                        Your pussy lips are drooling and you can feel Diva juices slowly running down your leg.
                        You are panting from the feeling in your neck and you desire more, Diva too, so on a common nod you get to step two.
                        You start to grind your wet cunt against Diva’s, both of you moaning in each other neck.
                        Blood is good but blood and sex is simply divine.
                        Your pussies are literally eating each others seeking for a cock that is not there as you feel your vagina pulse with delightful pleasure, every single nerve aflame.
                        Both of you slide against each other for several minutes, never parting away as a constant fountain of female fluids runs down your respective legs.
                        Diva wings are flapping wildly behind her <if test="player.wings.type == VAMPIRE">, yours too and you try not to take flight as a the winds created by your combined flapping shake the tent</if>.
                        The both of you scream in ecstasy breaking out of the bite, blood still dripping from each other chin as you and Diva reach your orgasm.
                        Unsatisfied the both of you keep at it for several hours. After about the sixth orgasm
                    </elseif>
                </if>

                You start to doze off tired as Diva pull you down in her coffin still embracing you.

                You wake up in the morning, still hugging with Diva. She’s fast asleep but still wearing a content smile.
            </text>
        </lib>
        <lib name="talkMenu">
            <text name="menu">
                <i>“Oh? What thou want to talk about? I have things to do but I can take a few minutes.”</i>
            </text>
            <text name="vampirism">
                Seriously why does she need blood to survive anyway. Couldn't she just eat a steak like everyone?

                <i>
                    “Thou may not know but my very fragile stomach does not allow any other form of nutrition.
                    I wouldn't be able to eat like the others even if I wanted to.”
                </i>

                So she literally get sick when eating normal food… well that's sad for her. What about garlic?

                <i>“Simple allergy, nothing more.”</i>

                Is her issue contagious?

                <i>
                    “Not unless you drink some of my blood or blood I drank from.
                    My bite is not viral but can leave my prey weak and some time close to death from blood loss.
                    Now if thou would excuse me I need to prepare for tonight.”
                </i>

                You nod and let the vampire to her thing going back to yours.
            </text>
            <text name="sunlight">
                So, something came to your attention… why exactly does she hate sunlight.

                <i>“It’s bad for my skin… also bright light just outright hurt my eyes. I’m almost blind at day and when I’m not I have to constantly cover my eyes to be able to see anything ahead of me.”</i>

                So it's not because she will turn to ashes or anything of the stories.

                <i>“If you’re talking about vampire tales from foreign lands I will have you know I’m alive just like you are. I just happen to have a body closer to bats and nocturnal creatures then I do to the daywalkers. As far as it goes the only trait I share with your so called mythical vampire is that whenever I drink a lot of blood I begin to develop magical powers and tremendous strength. I know for a fact I age at a slowed rate although I will likely still die when I get too old, I only have an extended lifespan rather than true immortality. Furthermore drinking heals my wounds quickers thanks to my ability to swiftly metabolise food to repair my damaged tissue.”</i>

                Well, now that you think of it, you wonder if meeting a vampire who has none of the standard weaknesses but the strength of a woman five time her size is any better then the monster of legends told of in Ingnam. You leave to ponder on this somewhat creepy question.
            </text>
            <text name="her">
                Now that you think of it was she always a vampire?

                <i>“No...In the same way as most adventurers I used to be a human and came here by accident about 30 years ago. Truth be told Mareth was already a hell of a mess back then.”</i>

                So what happened anyway?

                <i>“The demons happened, some crazed freak with horns caught me while I was sleeping and brought me to his laboratory to experiment on me. Said something along the line of creating a new variety of demonic servant for Lethice and that he did as he toyed with my body for an entire month using both corruptive material and modified transformative items. Regardless, the incubus messed up badly because not only I awoke in a bloodcrazed rage, but I pretty much drank him dry along with his other test subjects. He had three orgasms by the time I was done and I was not going to hold back after being starved from food for an entire month.”</i>

                This explains the aphrodisiacs in her bite and her fleeting magical talents if not absurd strength. Well at least she didn’t get her vampirism out of nowhere.
            </text>
            <text name="vialofliquid">
                You ask Diva if she would mind giving you some blood.

                <if test="player.batScore() gt 6 or player.vampireScore() gt 6">
				She blush with embarrassment and reply <i>“Thy know thou could've just asked to drink straight from the tap I wouldn’t had minded. Perhaps another time.”</i>
				<else>
				<i>“I wouldn’t mind [name] but be warned that it is highly infectious.”</i>
				</else>
				</if>

                She hands to you a vial right away.
            </text>
        </lib>
    </lib>
    <lib name="item">
        <!-- TODO @Oxdeception: move this section? -->
        <lib name="useText">
            <text name="first">
                Ew! This thing is indeed blood. It tastes awful, a strong, coppery taste, the liquid is thick from the iron content.
                As you try to get the taste out of your mouth, you feel something begin to change in you.
            </text>
            <text name="vampire">
                The blood tastes wonderful, as always.
                You have downed the whole vial much sooner than you would have liked.
                <if test="silly()">You filthy druggie.</if>
                Leaving you wishing for more even as the vampiric blood starts changing your body further.
            </text>
            <text name="pure">
                The blood tastes awful, a strong, coppery taste, and is thick from the iron content.
                Yet, under the blood’s metallic aftertaste, there's a hint of sweetness to it that you can’t really put your finger on.
                As you try to get the taste out of your mouth, you feel your body starting to change.
            </text>
            <text name="normal">
                You uncork the vial and down it’s contents.
                You gag disgusted as the thick, metallic tang of blood coats your throat.
                <if test="silly()">What else were you expecting with that label and smell? Tomato juice with iron shavings?</if>
                With some effort, you force down the blood and swallow it.
                A rush of heat flows through your veins as your body starts to react to the new blood.
            </text>
        </lib>
        <lib name="tfText">
            <text name="wings.type">
                <if test="$pure">
                    <if test="player.wings.type eq BAT_LIKE_LARGE">
                        As you finish the blood, intense pain flares in your wing-arms.
                        You drop the vial, the empty reinforced glass tinkling as it bounces on the ground.
                        You cry out as your arms creak and twist, your bones breaking down and reforming in a frenzy.
                        Your parchment-like skin begins to fall off in clumps, leaving the mess of malformed bones that are your arms right now naked for all to see.
                        However, even as you watch, dark blood creeps over the bone, properly aligning them before healing them over, although not in their old form.
                        Within seconds, the pain is gone, as your bones are remade into ones alike those you were born with, in structure if nothing else, the eldritch power of your blood finally ebbing away, but not before the last of it settles and turns into a brand new patch of skin.
                        It's still sensitive, but you'll get used to it.
                        You catch something moving on the edge of your peripheral vision, causing your hard-won instincts to kick in, muscle memory forcing you into a lunge away from whatever it was before you’re even fully aware of what’s happening.
                        Instead of dodging with your usual grace, you stumble and roll, landing on your wings… Wait, wings??
                        It seems that, while you were fascinated by your bloody shenanigans, you failed to notice that you were growing wings.
                        Understandable, since your arms breaking themselves several times over tends to take priority over such things, attention-wise.
                        You shakily stand up, your balance still thrown off by the new limb, inwardly grumbling at how long is it going to take you to get used to them. Distracted as you are, both from the ordeal and your inner grumbling, your first attempt at walking inevitably ends with an intimate reunion of your face and the ground.
                        This time, you don’t bother to keep your cursing to the confines of your own mind.
                        <else>
                            <if test="player.isVampire()">
                                As soon as the last drop of blood passes your now crimson lips, a terrible pain flares in the center of your back, a pain so intense that you black out briefly, coming back to your senses as you hit your head against the ground.
                                You hear a horrifying ripping noise as your back stretches and tears to allow new bones to expand, black as tar and far lighter than most of the bones in your body.
                                These new bones shift under your shoulder blade skin as you fall on all groaning in pain and clawing at the ground.
                                In a flash of pain they violently break out of your skin sending blood everywhere as you make a chilling scream your wounds slowly closing on their own.
                                Still panting from the pain, you take a look at your new appendage.
                                It's a pair of large vampire wings of impressive size.
                                Feeling chilly you fold them back on your body and you ought to admit they indeed look like a large cape.
                                <else>
                                    You drop the vial, the glass shattering, as intense pain flares around your shoulder blades.
                                    The pain intensifies, causing you to drop to the ground, clawing and screaming in agony as your back suddenly explodes with a wet ripping noise, blood splattering around you as a large pair of black leathery wings emerge from the bloody ruin that is your back right now, stretching to their full span.
                                    The pain finally starts to recede, leaving a bone-deep weariness in it’s wake.
                                    After a while, you manage to recover enough to be sure that trying to stand up won’t result in graceless, and painful, flopping, so you do just that, wrapping your new wings around you on instinct as you rise.
                                    Huh, wrapped like this you could probably pass them off as a long cape so long as nobody looks too closely, but you are certain they are the real deal.
                                    After all that pain, flying better be worth it.
                                </else>
                            </if>
                        </else>
                    </if>
                    <b>You will be able to enjoy nightly flight using your brand new vampire wings.</b>
                    <else>
                        Large bones surge out of your wrists and elbows.
                        You can feel your bones shifting and grinding all over your body as your skeletal structure begins changing into one more fit for a flying creature, with light, hollow bones.
                        You collapse to the ground as they begin shifting proportions becoming thinner and longer to maximize area while reducing their density.
                        Leathery flesh begins to cover your new bony protrusions, spreading between each of them like creeping moss.
                        Eventually, the skin stops growing and you admire your new arms.
                        They are very obviously bat wings. You close them around your waist, like this they could easily be mistaken for a large cape when seen from afar.
                        <b>You now have large bat wings.</b>
                    </else>
                </if>

            </text>
            <text name="ears.type">
                <if test="$pure">
                    <if test="player.earType ne Ears.HUMAN">
                        Before you can dwell on the implications of that, the changes continue.\n\n
                    </if>
                    Your ears begin to prickle as they elongate to a point, being now reminiscent of those of elves, goblins, or in your case, vampires. Aside from looking cute, you find your new ears have drastically improved your hearing.
                    <b>Sound has become an entirely new experience now that you have pointy vampire ears!</b>
                    <else>
                        Your ears begin to prickle and burn as the skin tears and stretches, changing into wide, deep ears, perfect for catching any stray sound. Which becomes apparent when your hearing becomes far more clear than it has ever been.
                        <b>Sound has become an entirely new experience now that you have bat ears!</b>
                    </else>
                </if>
            </text>
            <text name="eyes.type">
                Your eyes shift, causing sunlight to suddenly become annoyingly bright for you.
                It takes several minutes for your eyes to get used to it and, once they do, you still have to keep them half closed, so as to not be blinded by the sun’s glare.
                Upon looking at your reflection in the water, you discover your irises have taken on a blood-red shade.
                <b>You have Vampire Eyes.</b>
            </text>
            <text name="skinTone">
                Your skin suddenly starts itching, causing you to look at it just in time for you to see it finish paling into a shade that wouldn’t be out of place on a corpse.
                You feel sleepy… horribly so, but you dismiss it as being the fault of the glaring light above your head.
                <b>You guess you could use some extra sunlight with your pale skin.</b>
            </text>
            <text name="rearBody.type">
                You drop the vial, the glass shattering as it hits the ground, as an intense itching sets in around your neck.
                Bringing your hands to your neck to scratch it, you find sparse, downy fuzz.
                As you scratch away, it continues lengthening and growing in density until you have a collar of fur around your neck.
                Well, this isn’t so bad, the scarf-like look is certainly nice, at the very least.
                <b>Your neck now sports a collar of fur.</b>
            </text>
            <text name="faceType">
                You yelp as a throbbing pain takes root in the sides of your mouth.
                You feel your canines grow longer as your throat grow dryer.
                You could go for some wine right now, with a bloody steak to top it off… maybe just the steak.
                Or just the blood, really. You aren’t picky.
                Really, it’s up to you whether just rip off some poor sod’s throat and drink straight from the tap or drink blood from a wineglass, what with <b>your new vampire fangs!</b>
            </text>
            <text name="noChange">Odd.  You don't feel any different.</text>
        </lib>
    </lib>
</story>